[
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which of these is one of the ancient wonders of the world?",
    "choice1": "The Temple of Luxor",
    "choice2": "Karnak",
    "choice3": "Great Pyramid of Giza",
    "choice4": "The Sphinx",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder is located in Ephesus?",
    "choice1": "The Lighthouse",
    "choice2": "The Hanging Garden",
    "choice3": "The Mausoleum",
    "choice4": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "The Temple of Artemis is dedicated to the goddess of?",
    "choice1": "The Hunt",
    "choice2": "Harvest",
    "choice3": "Wisdom",
    "choice4": "Home",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When was the Lighthouse of Alexandria built?",
    "choice1": "1200 BC",
    "choice2": "250 BC",
    "choice3": "300 AD",
    "choice4": "950 AD",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder does legend say was created by Nebuchadnezzar?",
    "choice1": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice2": "The Mausoleum",
    "choice3": "The Hanging Gardens of Babylon",
    "choice4": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "If you wanted to visit Babylon today, which nation would you have to visit?",
    "choice1": "Iraq",
    "choice2": "Afghanistan",
    "choice3": "Egypt",
    "choice4": "Turkey",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Who was the Mausoleum built for?",
    "choice1": "Ptolemy",
    "choice2": "King David",
    "choice3": "King Solomon",
    "choice4": "Mausolus",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder of the ancient world was designed by Satyros and Pythius?",
    "choice1": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "choice2": "The Great Pyramid of Giza",
    "choice3": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice4": "Mausoleum",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder was designed by Chares of Lindros?",
    "choice1": "Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "choice2": "Statue of Zeus at Olympia",
    "choice3": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice4": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder was sculpted by Phidias?",
    "choice1": "Statue of Zeus at Olympia",
    "choice2": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "choice3": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice4": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "If you wanted to see the site where the Mausoleum had been built, which country would you have to visit?",
    "choice1": "Yemen",
    "choice2": "Turkey",
    "choice3": "Egypt",
    "choice4": "Iran",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which is the only wonder still standing?",
    "choice1": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "choice2": "Great Pyramid of Giza",
    "choice3": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice4": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "In 1994, archeologists were able to find the remnants of which ancient wonder?",
    "choice1": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "choice2": "The Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "choice3": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice4": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder was destroyed a vainglorious act of arson by Herostratus?",
    "choice1": "The Temple of Artemis",
    "choice2": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "choice3": "The Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "choice4": "Hanging Gardens of Babylon",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which wonder's stones were used to build the Citadel of Qaitbay?",
    "choice1": "The Statue of Zeus",
    "choice2": "The Great Pyramid",
    "choice3": "The Hanging Garden of Babylon",
    "choice4": "The Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "answer": 4
  }
]